magnium-themes.com 2018-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Magnium Themes - Premium WordPress, WooCommerce, Magento and OpenCart responsive retina themes

## Who we are

Our website address is: http://magniumthemes.com/

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

Information submitted through the contact form on our site is sent to our company email, hosted by Gmail. Google adheres to the EU/US “Privacy Shield” policy and you can find more information about this here: [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks).

These submissions are only kept for customer service purposes they are never used for marketing purposes or shared with third parties.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics on our site for anonymous reporting of site usage. So, no personalized data is stored. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics monitoring your behavior on our site please use this link: [Google Analytics Opt-out/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

## Third Party Access To Your Data

We don’t share your data with third-parties in a way as to reveal any of your personal information like email, name, etc. The only exceptions to that rule are for partners we have to share limited data with in order to provide the services you expect from us. Please see below:

### Envato Pty Ltd

For the purpose of validating and getting your purchase information regarding licenses for the Avada theme, we send your provided tokens and purchase keys to Envato Pty Ltd and use the response from their API to register your validated support data. See the Envato privacy policy here: [Envato Privacy Policy](https://envato.com/privacy/).

### Zendesk

Zendesk provides the support ticketing platform we use to handle support requests. The data they receive is limited to the data you explicitly provide and consent to being set when you create a support ticket. Zendesk adheres to the EU/US “Privacy Shield” and you can see their privacy policy here: [Zendesk Privacy Policy](https://www.zendesk.com.ru/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/).

### MailChimp

If you sign up to our newletter, using our newsletter form that is hosted by MailChimp (on their server), your email address as well as the marketing reasons to contact you for, will be stored by MailChimp. You have to give explicit consent to all marketing means you want us to use to contact you. For more information on MailChimp’s privacy policy, please see here: [MailChimp Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Contact information

If you have any questions or want to remove your personal data please contact us at [support@magniumthemes.com](mailto:support@magniumthemes.comz)
